<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Events on Grupa Wolne</title><link>https://grupawolne.pl/en/events/</link><description>Recent content in Events on Grupa Wolne</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>pl-pl</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 12:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://grupawolne.pl/en/events/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ZIN/UKRAINE</title><link>https://grupawolne.pl/en/zin/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://grupawolne.pl/en/zin/</guid><description>As Grupa Wolne we would like to invite you to work together on a zine. From the 9th of September until the end of December we are going to meet every friday evening in Baza Inclsv in order to learn certain aspects of group work and editorial activities - in practice! At the same time, we are announcing an open call for the works from which we will create the first issue of our paper.</description></item><item><title>Free Drawings</title><link>https://grupawolne.pl/en/art/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://grupawolne.pl/en/art/</guid><description>Art course with elements of art therapy. We want to create a safe space where you can express yourself, try, explore, make &amp;ldquo;mistakes&amp;rdquo; and be creative. The most important thing for us is the process, not the end result, therefore we invite participants to take part in the entire course, not just individual classes. We will adapt the program of classes to your needs and interests. We invite both people who want to draw and paint for pure pleasure and those who want to apply for art studies and need to prepare a portfolio.</description></item><item><title>Thursdays Off</title><link>https://grupawolne.pl/en/thursdays-off/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://grupawolne.pl/en/thursdays-off/</guid><description>Thursdays Off is a weekly, free event to which we invite young people, who have experienced migration, but not only. We meet at 5 PM at Inclsv Buzz at Zbawiciela Square. We have a base and free time on our hands, what happens next depends on the weather and on what we want to do. On sunny days, we will offer you trips and games in the open air: bicycles, walks, Frisbee, bonfires.</description></item></channel></rss>